That
[ __ ] Bhaiya, I have got your grocery order, will you
send it to someone to get it, okay, should I do
Paytm, put a chilli in it,
I gave it to you, perfect som
digital, in this we
can transfer money to someone, we
can ask for it from someone and after soul to quit,
many people who earlier believed in taste
or believed in offline,
they adopted online transfer your wallet
sapna error UPI, so we came out
in the digital age, so if you talk about the activity on our phones,
as
we are moving towards the digital age, we do
online transactions, so one thing
you have to be very careful that there are so many oppositions too, so for that
we will talk about
how you can protect yourself from the front,
how can a person take care of cyber security so that
your data is
not compromised somewhere,
how can you protect your password and how the
name that you have been hearing while growing up, that
person should not cross with us, you must have seen the
video going viral in the background, he is a street
singer, he was singing a song when something happened  If things go
wrong and he wants to join Biscuit Music School, then for
his donation
he had put a cut which
he had told that thank you for your
contribution, all these
options are there on Paytm ji, he had given the phone number of 113 Music School,
so you are seeing how I mean where were
we and for a week he used to do science and everything else,
here everything
that you can think of
is online, due to this I would like to tell
that we were going to a friend's wedding,
four years ago we had already started,
so we could not meet him, I
saw from a distance, first of all, I saw a lookalike,
so we did Paytm to him, it was their
lift that if you want to
punish someone then come to me, they had
launched Paytm, we did Sadan, so
brother, Choli Living and Disappear and
get more from * Search for words, so to
avoid friends, what is the end, we will
talk about it, if my name is
Ling Ko Chiku, I am a certified financial
planner, in the next  I make videos so that you and
your parents can like them and
become more so because our company's side is
cricketing world famous, it has its own advantages, we
relate all these things, online
passport, dress
code, disadvantages of using all that, so last year CR
could also have recorded 135 complaints of
online fraud in Nashik Crime Record Bureau of Indian, if compared to 2018, then
11.8% is promised, so it will keep increasing
as we are moving towards digital path, so
what is the way to avoid this,
first of all do not let KYC identity fraud happen to you, it is
very good for you
because when we go to the bank, there is a time when we do
not go to the bank, all the work is done sitting at home
on the phone, internet banking, phone banking,
UP iSlab, so always keep in mind that the
bank has fabric console
available for you, which will call so that we are
calling from your bank that you have to do KYC, then
take your document, an OTP will come on your phone,
share it, it will be
necessary to give it, otherwise you will be in the comment box,
I  Whenever you see such a thing,
you should strike that something
is wrong with Yes Bank and at any time,
stand on call of the hospital's cardiologist, whoever is there will be
called back if any resident
needs help, they do not call and say that
we have seen many KYCs done in Paytm
every day, you have come to this Lanka and
people have taken money from your account and money has been withdrawn from your account,
then you should not share your KYC documents
with anyone, be it tea or
WhatsApp, so upload it on
Don 2-The, never encourage
anyone to go and visit, there
is definitely a left but again, due to such things, Bigg
Boss is seen, people work, many smart people,
they are also trapped in these fronts,
because of Infosys, this last money, your vice chief
documents go, still bring the tally
or click on the office link, similarly, they will
give any details anywhere and do
not click on any external links at all,
login on third party device, do not use your personal information
spicy of your bank account,
now log in  If for some
reason you have to do some unavoidable circumstance then you
must do it fully.
Another point is that you have old passwords
which we adjust many times and
give them just like that. You usually
check this on online sale. Do you
log out of your phone details?
All our Gmail accounts, all our bank
net banking passwords are just for the sake of it. We
keep these passwords as a
superhit so that we don't have to enter them again and again. Then
we forget, so the old phone is giving the answer,
mixed and some of it is logged out,
some of it is real. Everything is sent from your account only. If you
login once, then the
entire data can go to him, so mix
and do log out properly. So keep this thing in
mind so that you
use verified ones. Whenever you are downloading any app,
first check whether it is verified or
not because your data is getting
compromised. When you are
entering details, then all the data is to be provided more. So
please like and share my side of  Is there
any such girl or
not, then here you can download it so that
money can be debited from your account without you knowing
what is
happening, so that is also an important thing to set and if you are
logging in then
log in from a secure website which has HTTPS in front, all this is an effort to
make hot nude art
clips from password, the password you keep
online because you
keep passwords everywhere, so whatever password you keep,
change it from time to time and
keep a strong password, you will
see that no one can guess that it
is your password and everything will be compromised in 1 minute,
so
keep the from passport on the text message, I
prepare from passport, there are
many applications, so what
I do is use LastPass, you will
find applications, you will
search online for an application that saves passwords,
where your data
is encrypted, your data is from the
address itself, you will
not have any problem of forgetting the password  And you will be
able to keep the password for yourself. Next, do
not click on any link. This time, the
maximum number of times that usually happen is that
you have Kolkata on Friday. You
can plan your investment
near your village. The network
entries will become normal. Your credit card will be locked.
Click on the previous link. Do
not write anything on this channel, otherwise click on download.
Then it will not verify. And you are not sure whether
it is related to you for the exam
or not. There are related people present on it. If
you do not know how to use UPI, then
first learn it because what happens is that
many times if someone
makes some payment through WhatsApp or any third party payment, then
it will bring it to you. For making the payment,
you have to provide the UPI
pack. If you do not know, then it is possible that
now you will also have to verify the calling due to which
you are receiving more calls.
If you want to receive something, then there is
no need for any OTP, it
comes automatically because some such
calls were also going out saying, is this transfer of roti,
give me roti?  If there is no need then first see
you by half hearted, this is easy to use,
learn it once, whoever is sitting at home, whom you
can tell the whole thing to, then
take that too and as much as possible, the
best thing is returning, anything
related to transactions, I
would like to say that whatever you do,
everything needs to be expensive, now whether you are crossing the road
or driving a car, whatever you are doing, the
money is there in everything and whatever
we do digitally is unavoidable, that
means anyone has to stay with us, if they
convince us then its advantages and
disadvantages and before that we
can do it in minutes, when we will be alert
and when we will take care of all these points,
we will not do any, this is a great article
and will take care of all these things
and also tell your family members that if
something like this happens then you will get this
on your phone, then I have given a lot of smart
looks, let's see who
goes along with the circle of digital fraud, due to which
you do not know, in this much time
Prince and  It seems that everything is in
automatic cars, you don't even know
when and from where the money gets debited,
accounts get frozen, you have to get a credit card,
then you also
start all accounts on Tuesday technology
and digital properties, now we are on managing your
money but again at the same time try to keep in mind that there is an
inverter, so these were some comments
from the side that how can you sip, tell
Sita anything from the side of digital cyber crime
in the comment section, if you have got any
accident set up somewhere then tell that too,
superhit everybody can get benefit,
so now any reminder, you have not subscribed to the channel yet, do
subscribe to my
channel, you will get it in the next video,
okay now so
[music]
[laughter]